"use strict";(self.webpackChunkquiz_game=self.webpackChunkquiz_game||[]).push([[523,255],{523:function(e,r,n){n.r(r),n.d(r,{default:function(){return x}});var t=n(885),s=n(791),i=n(577),o=[{question:"Who is the main protagonist of Top Gun: Maverick?",id:1,options:[{answer:"Steve Carell",correct:!1,id:11},{answer:"Tom Cruise",correct:!0,id:44},{answer:"Jean-Claude Van Damme",correct:!1,id:33},{answer:"James P. Sullivan",correct:!1,id:22}]},{question:"Which option is a quote from the Fast and Furious franchise?",id:2,options:[{answer:"What a lame franchise",correct:!1,id:11},{answer:"Vin Diesel was born to be bald",correct:!1,id:33},{answer:"Ride or die",correct:!0,id:44},{answer:"Die or ride",correct:!1,id:22}]},{question:"Were Ross and Rachel on a break in Friends TV Series?",id:3,options:[{answer:"How dare u ask that",correct:!1,id:11},{answer:"They were on a breaaaaak",correct:!1,id:33},{answer:"Not really",correct:!1,id:22},{answer:"There is no clear answer to this question to this day",correct:!0,id:44}]},{question:"Is Interstellar movie about interstellar travel?",id:4,options:[{answer:"No, it is about environmental problems",correct:!1,id:11},{answer:"Yes, it mostly is",correct:!0,id:44},{answer:"No, it is about Star Wars",correct:!1,id:33},{answer:"No, it is about Michael Caine being old",correct:!1,id:22}]},{question:"What is the complete name of the Thor movie released in the year 2022?",id:5,options:[{answer:"Thor: Love and I can not be bothered",correct:!1,id:11},{answer:"Thor: Love and Death ",correct:!1,id:33},{answer:"Thor: Love and Thunder",correct:!0,id:44},{answer:"Thor: Love and The Douchebag",correct:!1,id:22}]},{question:"Which movie below is based on a novel?",id:6,options:[{answer:"The Green Mile",correct:!0,id:44},{answer:"Toy story 4",correct:!1,id:11},{answer:"Pitch perfect",correct:!1,id:33},{answer:"Ted",correct:!1,id:22}]},{question:"What did the movie I Am Mother focus on?",id:7,options:[{answer:"A mother",correct:!1,id:11},{answer:"Artificial intelligence",correct:!0,id:44},{answer:"War",correct:!1,id:33},{answer:"Climate change",correct:!1,id:22}]},{question:"Who is batman?",id:8,options:[{answer:"Superman",correct:!1,id:11},{answer:"I think he is Harley Quinn",correct:!1,id:33},{answer:"He is a horse actually",correct:!1,id:22},{answer:"A man dressed as a bat",correct:!0,id:44}]},{question:"Was lightning McQueen the fastest car in the Cars movie released in the year 2006?",id:9,options:[{answer:"No, actually he was the fastest moron",correct:!1,id:11},{answer:"Yes he was",correct:!0,id:44},{answer:"No, Not as fast as Doc Hudson",correct:!1,id:33},{answer:"No, Chick Hicks was",correct:!1,id:22}]},{question:"Hugh Jackman is most famous for what exactly?",id:10,options:[{answer:"Playing as Wolverine",correct:!0,id:44},{answer:"Being a good boy",correct:!1,id:11},{answer:"Playing as Darth vader",correct:!1,id:33},{answer:"Being Australian",correct:!1,id:22}]},{question:"Which movie is not a sci-fi film?",id:11,options:[{answer:"Road To Perdition",correct:!0,id:44},{answer:"Dune",correct:!1,id:11},{answer:"Chappie",correct:!1,id:33},{answer:"12 Monkeys",correct:!1,id:22}]},{question:"Which one in not a member of The Simpson family?",id:12,options:[{answer:"Homer",correct:!1,id:11},{answer:"Marge",correct:!0,id:33},{answer:"Moe",correct:!1,id:44},{answer:"Lisa",correct:!1,id:22}]},{question:"Which one is a famous quote from the joker?",id:13,options:[{answer:"All you care about is chicken nuggies",correct:!1,id:11},{answer:"Let us put a smile on that face",correct:!1,id:33},{answer:"Why so serious",correct:!0,id:44},{answer:"I love you batman",correct:!1,id:22}]},{question:"Did they save Mark Watney at the end of The Martian?",id:14,options:[{answer:"No, they left him to rot there",correct:!1,id:11},{answer:"He was high, so he was not on mars , just high",correct:!1,id:33},{answer:"No they hated him",correct:!1,id:22},{answer:"Yes, yes they did",correct:!0,id:44}]},{question:"Did you like Scarlett Johansson in The Prestige?",id:15,options:[{answer:"No, I hate her in general",correct:!1,id:11},{answer:"meh...",correct:!1,id:33},{answer:"Yes, Chose this option if you want to win the game",correct:!0,id:44},{answer:"No, the hell with her",correct:!1,id:22}]},{question:"Which movie did tom cruise not star in?",id:16,options:[{answer:"Mission: Impossible 1",correct:!1,id:11},{answer:"Mission: Impossible 2",correct:!1,id:33},{answer:"Mission: Possible 4",correct:!1,id:22},{answer:"Mission: Impossible 3",correct:!0,id:44}]},{question:"Chris Evans is most famous for playing as:",id:17,options:[{answer:"Captain America",correct:!0,id:44},{answer:"Captain Italia",correct:!1,id:11},{answer:"Hot guy in in The Nanny Diaries",correct:!1,id:33},{answer:"Some lame movie I do not even remember",correct:!1,id:22}]},{question:"Who is more famous , Chris Hemsworth or Me?",id:18,options:[{answer:"Omg, you are",correct:!1,id:11},{answer:"Chris, Chris is more famous buddy",correct:!0,id:44},{answer:"Takes courage to ask such thing",correct:!1,id:33},{answer:"You can not be serious?",correct:!1,id:22}]},{question:"So , Don't Look Up , what is it about?",id:19,options:[{answer:"It is about boring me to death",correct:!1,id:11},{answer:"Blah blah",correct:!1,id:33},{answer:"It is more than just an asteroid heading towards the earth",correct:!0,id:44},{answer:"meh...",correct:!1,id:22}]},{question:"Which one is not a comic character?",id:20,options:[{answer:"Bruce wayne",correct:!1,id:11},{answer:"Selina kyle",correct:!1,id:33},{answer:"Lex luthor",correct:!1,id:22},{answer:"The real slim shady",correct:!0,id:44}]}],c=n(442),a=function(){var e=arguments.length>0&&void 0!==arguments[0]?arguments[0]:function(){},r=(0,s.useState)([]),n=(0,t.Z)(r,2),a=n[0],d=n[1],u=(0,s.useState)(!0),l=(0,t.Z)(u,2),h=l[0],m=l[1];(0,s.useEffect)((function(){f()}),[]);var f=function(){m(!0),setTimeout((function(){d((0,i.Nu)(o,c.zF)),e(),m(!1)}),1e3)};return{loading:h,result:a}},d=n(176),u=n(561),l=n(184),h=function(e){var r=e.limit,n=e.num,t=e.setNum,i=e.count,o=(0,s.useRef)(),a=function(){return t((function(e){return e<=0?r:e-1}))};return(0,s.useEffect)((function(){return o.current=setInterval(a,1e3),function(){return clearInterval(o.current)}}),[]),(0,s.useEffect)((function(){if(i===c.zF)return t(0),function(){return clearInterval(o.current)}}),[i]),(0,l.jsx)("div",{children:(0,l.jsx)(d.X2,{className:"text-center",children:(0,l.jsx)(u.F,{xs:"12",sm:"4",md:"3",lg:"2",children:(0,l.jsx)(d.Zb,{className:"timer-card",children:(0,l.jsx)(d.eW,{children:(0,l.jsxs)("h4",{className:"timer-num",children:["Timer : ",n]})})})})})})},m=n(324),f=function(e){var r=e.options,n=e.num,o=e.createAnswerModel,a=e.removeOption,u=e.setRemoveOption,h=(0,s.useState)(""),m=(0,t.Z)(h,2),f=m[0],w=m[1],x=(0,s.useState)(r),j=(0,t.Z)(x,2),g=j[0],p=j[1];(0,s.useEffect)((function(){n===c.mo&&w("")}),[n]),(0,s.useEffect)((function(){p(r)}),[r]),(0,s.useEffect)((function(){a&&v()}),[a]);var v=function(){var e=[],r=g.find((function(e){return!0===e.correct})),n=g.filter((function(e){return!1===e.correct})),t=(0,i.Nu)(n,1);e.push(r),e.push(t[0]),p(e),u(!1)};return(0,l.jsx)("div",{children:(0,l.jsx)(d.eW,{children:g.map((function(e,r){return(0,l.jsx)("div",{className:"cursor--pointer question-text mt-4 question-option ".concat(e.id===f?"option-selected":""),tabindex:"1",onClick:function(){return r=e.id,n=e.correct,w(r),void o(r,n);var r,n},children:r+1+". "+e.answer})}))})})},w=n(255),x=function(){var e=a(),r=(0,s.useState)(0),n=(0,t.Z)(r,2),i=n[0],o=n[1],x=(0,s.useState)(c.mo),j=(0,t.Z)(x,2),g=j[0],p=j[1],v=(0,s.useState)([]),b=(0,t.Z)(v,2),N=b[0],y=b[1],q=(0,s.useState)(!1),F=(0,t.Z)(q,2),k=F[0],S=F[1],T=(0,s.useState)(!1),M=(0,t.Z)(T,2),W=M[0],C=M[1],A=(0,s.useState)(0),I=(0,t.Z)(A,2),Z=I[0],L=I[1],z=(0,s.useState)(!1),X=(0,t.Z)(z,2),D=X[0],E=X[1],H=null;(0,s.useEffect)((function(){e.loading||R()}),[g]),(0,s.useEffect)((function(){Z===c.A_&&(H=setTimeout((function(){L(0)}),1e3*g))}),[Z]);var R=function(){g===c.mo+Z&&i<c.zF&&(o(i+1),L(0))};return(0,l.jsx)("div",{children:e.loading?(0,l.jsx)(m.Z,{}):(0,l.jsxs)(l.Fragment,{children:[(0,l.jsx)("div",{children:i<c.zF?(0,l.jsx)(h,{count:i,num:g,setNum:p,limit:c.mo+Z}):(0,l.jsx)(d.X2,{className:"m-auto",children:(0,l.jsx)(u.F,{children:(0,l.jsx)(w.default,{data:e.result,selectedAnswers:N})})})}),i<c.zF&&(0,l.jsx)(d.X2,{className:"d-flex justify-content-center",children:(0,l.jsx)(u.F,{lg:"6",md:"10",children:(0,l.jsx)(d.Zb,{className:"question-card mt-3",children:(0,l.jsx)("div",{children:(0,l.jsxs)(d.eW,{children:[(0,l.jsx)(d.X2,{children:(0,l.jsx)(u.F,{sm:"12",children:(0,l.jsxs)("h4",{className:"question-text",children:[i+1," . ",e.result[i].question," "]})})}),(0,l.jsx)("div",{children:(0,l.jsx)(d.X2,{children:(0,l.jsx)(u.F,{sm:"12",children:(0,l.jsx)(f,{removeOption:k,setRemoveOption:S,num:g,createAnswerModel:function(){var r=arguments.length>0&&void 0!==arguments[0]?arguments[0]:"",n=arguments.length>1&&void 0!==arguments[1]&&arguments[1],t=N,s=e.result[i].id,o=null,a={questionId:s,optionId:r,correct:n,timeSpent:Z>0?c.mo-(g-Z):c.mo-g};if(N.length>0&&(o=t.find((function(e){return e.questionId===s}))),o){var d=t.indexOf(o);t.splice(d,1,a)}else t.push(a);y(t)},options:e.result[i].options})})})})]})})})})}),(0,l.jsx)("div",{className:"d-flex justify-content-center",children:i<c.zF&&(0,l.jsxs)(d.X2,{className:"d-flex justify-content-center",children:[(0,l.jsx)(u.F,{xs:"10",sm:"10",md:"12",lg:"12",children:(0,l.jsx)(d.zx,{className:"button-custom mt-2",onClick:function(){p(c.mo),L(0),clearTimeout(H)},children:"Next"})}),(0,l.jsx)(u.F,{xs:"10",sm:"10",md:"6",lg:"6",children:(0,l.jsx)(d.zx,{className:"button-lifeLine mt-2",disabled:W,onClick:function(){S(!0),C(!0)},children:"Remove Two Options"})}),(0,l.jsx)(u.F,{xs:"10",sm:"10",md:"6",lg:"6",children:(0,l.jsx)(d.zx,{className:"button-lifeLine mt-2",disabled:D,onClick:function(){E(!0),L(c.A_),p(g+c.A_)},children:"Add extra 10 seconds"})})]})})]})})}},255:function(e,r,n){n.r(r);var t=n(885),s=n(791),i=n(176),o=n(561),c=n(442),a=n(577),d=n(184);r.default=function(e){var r=e.selectedAnswers,n=(0,s.useState)(0),u=(0,t.Z)(n,2),l=u[0],h=u[1],m=(0,s.useState)(0),f=(0,t.Z)(m,2),w=f[0],x=f[1],j=(0,s.useState)(c.mo),g=(0,t.Z)(j,2),p=g[0],v=g[1],b=(0,s.useState)(c.mo),N=(0,t.Z)(b,2),y=N[0],q=N[1];return(0,s.useEffect)((function(){!function(e){var r=0,n=[];if(e.map((function(e){n.push(e.timeSpent),e.correct&&r++})),n.length>0){var t=Math.min.apply(Math,n),s=Math.max.apply(Math,n),i=(0,a.Y8)(n);x(t),v(s),q(i)}h(r)}(r)}),[]),(0,d.jsx)("div",{className:"d-flex justify-content-center",children:(0,d.jsx)(i.Zb,{className:"result-card",children:(0,d.jsxs)(i.eW,{children:[(0,d.jsx)("h4",{className:"mb-2",children:"Your Result"}),(0,d.jsx)(i.X2,{children:(0,d.jsx)(o.F,{children:(0,d.jsxs)("h4",{className:"result-text",children:["Number of correct answers : ",l]})})}),(0,d.jsx)(i.X2,{children:(0,d.jsx)(o.F,{children:(0,d.jsxs)("h4",{className:"result-text",children:["Number of incorrect answers :"," ",r.length-l]})})}),(0,d.jsx)(i.X2,{children:(0,d.jsx)(o.F,{children:(0,d.jsxs)("h4",{className:"result-text",children:["Number questions unanswered : ",10-r.length]})})}),r.length>0&&(0,d.jsxs)(d.Fragment,{children:[(0,d.jsx)("div",{className:"mt-4 mb-2",children:(0,d.jsx)("h4",{children:"Statistics About Answered Questions"})}),(0,d.jsx)(i.X2,{children:(0,d.jsx)(o.F,{children:(0,d.jsx)("h4",{className:"result-text",children:w<1?(0,d.jsx)(d.Fragment,{children:"Quickest answering time : Less than 1 second"}):(0,d.jsxs)(d.Fragment,{children:["Quickest answering time : ",w," second(s)"," "]})})})}),(0,d.jsx)(i.X2,{children:(0,d.jsx)(o.F,{children:(0,d.jsx)("h4",{className:"result-text",children:p<1?(0,d.jsx)(d.Fragment,{children:"Longest answering time : Less than 1 second"}):(0,d.jsxs)(d.Fragment,{children:["Longest answering time : ",p," second(s)"]})})})}),(0,d.jsx)(i.X2,{children:(0,d.jsx)(o.F,{children:(0,d.jsx)("h4",{className:"result-text",children:y<1?(0,d.jsx)(d.Fragment,{children:"Average answering time : Less than 1 second"}):(0,d.jsxs)(d.Fragment,{children:["Average answering time : ",y," second(s)"]})})})})]}),(0,d.jsx)(i.X2,{className:"d-flex justify-content-center mt-3",children:(0,d.jsx)(o.F,{md:"12",lg:"5",children:(0,d.jsx)(i.zx,{className:"button-custom mt-2",onClick:function(){return window.location.reload(!1)},children:"Try Again"})})})]})})})}},442:function(e,r,n){n.d(r,{A_:function(){return i},mo:function(){return t},zF:function(){return s}});var t=15,s=10,i=10},577:function(e,r,n){n.d(r,{Nu:function(){return t},Y8:function(){return s}});var t=function(){var e=arguments.length>0&&void 0!==arguments[0]?arguments[0]:[],r=arguments.length>1&&void 0!==arguments[1]?arguments[1]:0,n=[],t=[];if(e&&r)for(;n.length<r;)t.push(e.splice(Math.floor(Math.random()*e.length-1),1)[0]),n.push(t.pop());return n},s=function(e){var r=0;return e&&e.length>0&&(r=Math.round(function(e){var r=0;if(e)for(var n=0;n<e.length;n++)r+=e[n];return r}(e)/e.length)),r}}}]);
//# sourceMappingURL=523.2efa336b.chunk.js.map